in this lecture we will create the 3D
在这堂课中，我们将创建3D
text I click on the text tool I click on
我点击的文本工具上的文本
the canvas and type inkscape I use
我使用的画布和类型Inkscape
shrikan which is a free Google font I
这是一个免费的谷歌字体i
click on the select tool when I hold
按住鼠标左键时，单击选择工具
Ctrl I can easily change the size of the
Ctrl I可以轻松地更改
text I would like to curve the text to
文本我想要将文本弯曲成
do this I first have to convert the text
做到这一点，我首先要转换文本
to paths I go to path object to path to
转到我要转到的路径对象转到路径
curve the path I click on pathfx from
将我点击的路径绘制成曲线
the menu I choose Bend I click on the
我选择的菜单，折弯，我点击
edit on canvas icon now I see a green
在画布上编辑图标现在我看到一个绿色
line using the tool I can curve the line
用这个工具我可以画出一条直线
to finalize the effect I go to path
要最终确定效果，请转到Path
object to path I press the space bar I
对象到路径I按空格键I
go to my layers I call the path inkscape
转到我的层我称这条路径为Inkscape
now I want to give the text some depth
现在我想给这篇文章增加一些深度
to do this I go to extensions generate
要执行此操作，请转到扩展模块生成
from path long Shadow I click on live
从Path Long Shadow我点击LIVE
preview I set length to 2. I click on
预览我将长度设置为2。我点击
apply and on close we see below the text
应用并关闭时，我们将在文本下方看到
I have a group like before I want this
我有一个和以前一样的团体，我想要这个
group to be a single path I open the
将组设置为单路径我打开
group I click on the top path I drag the
组I单击顶部路径，然后拖动
scroll bar to the bottom and I
滚动条到底部，然后我
shift-click on the bottom path now that
现在按住Shift键并单击底部路径
all paths are selected I go to path
所有路径都已选中，我将转到路径
Union I make the path thirty percent
联合我让这条路走上30%
gray I call the path gray inkscape like
灰色的我称这条小路为灰色的墨迹
illustrator is very good at making
Illustrator非常擅长制作
groups but I don't need them to be in a
小组，但我不需要他们在一个
group so I right click on the top group
组，所以我用鼠标右键单击顶部组
and choose ungroup and I right click on
然后选择Ungroup(解组)，我右击
the folder where gray is in and choose
格雷所在的文件夹，然后选择
ungroup
解组
now I duplicate gray I lower the
现在我复制灰色，我降低
duplicate one step I make the path blue
重复一步，我让小路变蓝
I call the path light blue I zoom in
我把放大的那条路叫做淡蓝色
hold Ctrl and drag the blue path below
按住Ctrl键并将蓝色路径拖动到下方
the gray path
灰色的小路
in my layers I place blue below Gray
在我的层次中，我把蓝色放在灰色下面
I hold Ctrl and drag the blue path up
我按住Ctrl键并向上拖动蓝色路径
until it is roughly a quarter of the
直到它大约是
size of Gray
灰色的大小
I click on fill and stroke I change the
我点击填充和描边，然后更改
color a bit more to Blue
颜色要比蓝色多一点
now I duplicate gray I click on Lower to
现在我复制灰色，我点击下方
bottom I go to path Dynamic offset I
底部I转到路径动态偏移I
click on the Node tool above the letter
单击字母上方的节点工具
K there is a no I drag the note up to
K有一个no，我将便条拖到
make the path larger
让道路更宽阔
to finalize the effect I go to path
要最终确定效果，请转到Path
object to path I hide the other paths I
对象到路径I隐藏其他路径I
see the new shape has some holes in it
看到新形状上有一些洞了吗？
to remove them I go to path break apart
为了去掉它们，我去了Path Breaked
then I go to path Union I will make the
然后我去PATH联盟，我会做
path a darker blue I drag the blue a bit
一条深蓝色的小路我拖着蓝色走了一点
more to cyan I call the path dark blue I
更青色的是，我称这条小路为深蓝色
want a shape to go from dark blue to
我想要一个形状从深蓝色到
light blue
浅蓝色
I right click on dark blue and choose
我右击深蓝色，然后选择
set clip group I click on the pen tool I
设置剪贴组我单击钢笔工具I
click on the canvas click somewhere else
在画布上单击其他位置
and press enter I now have a line I
然后按Enter键我现在有一行I
click on the Node tool when I drag the
拖动时，单击节点工具
line in the middle I can bend the line I
中间的那条线我可以把这条线折弯
will drag the end nodes outside the dark
会将末端节点拖到黑暗之外
blue area at the bottom left I will
左下角的蓝色区域我会
increase the width of the line to about
将线条的宽度增加到大约
75. I click on the dropper tool and
75.我点击滴管工具，然后
shift-click on light blue I will call
按住Shift键并单击浅蓝色，我将呼叫
the path light blue line I click on fill
我点击填充的路径淡蓝色线条
and stroke and click on stroke paint I
和笔划，然后单击笔划画笔I
set blur to 30. I click on the Node tool
将模糊设置为30。我单击节点工具
to get the curve right I drag the lineup
为了得到正确的曲线，我拖拽阵容
to move the line I press Ctrl a to
要移动行，请按Ctrl a键以
select both nodes then I drag one of the
选择这两个节点，然后拖动其中一个
nodes
节点
I want to be able to drag the text
我希望能够拖动文本
independent from the gradient so I
独立于渐变，所以我
select the text related paths and group
选择与文本相关的路径和组
them now I can move the text up to get a
现在我可以将文本上移以获得
more 3D look I also want the gradient to
更3D的外观，我也想要渐变
be 3D so I duplicate it I drag the
是3D的，所以我复制它，我拖着
duplicate on top in the layer and click
在层的顶部复制，然后单击
on Lower to bottom I go to extensions
在从下到下的页面上，我转到扩展
generate from path long Shadow I set
从我设置的路径生成长阴影
length to 7. I click on apply and on
长度设置为7。我点击Apply，然后打开
close I place the group on the bottom as
关闭，我把这组放在底部
before I will unify the 3d effect into a
在我将3D效果统一到一个
single path I open the group I click on
打开我点击的组的单一路径
the top path I drag the scroll bar to
我将滚动条拖到的顶部路径
the bottom and I shift-click on the
我在底部按住Shift键并单击
bottom path I go to path Union and as
底部路径I转到路径UNION和AS
before I don't need them to be in a
在我不需要他们在一个
group so I right click on the top group
组，所以我用鼠标右键单击顶部组
and choose ungroup
并选择取消分组
and I right click on the folder where
我用鼠标右键点击文件夹
the 3d effect is in and choose ungroup I
3D效果在中，然后选择取消分组
will call the New Path long Shadow I go
我将把新的道路称为长影我走
to fill and stroke and make long Shadow
填充、描边和制作长阴影
a bit darker to see the long Shadow
看《长影》要暗一点
better I will add a gradient I will use
更好的做法是添加一个我将使用的渐变
dark blue for that I make dark blue
深蓝色为此我做了深蓝色
black I call the path gradient I go to
我把我要去的路径称为黑色渐变
fill and stroke I set blur to 25 I will
填充和描边我将模糊设置为25我会
use long Shadow to clip the gradient I
使用长阴影来剪裁渐变
right click on it and choose set clip
右键单击它，然后选择Set Clip
group I drag gradient in the clip group
剪贴组中的组I拖动渐变
I lower its opacity to 75 percent
我把它的不透明度降低到75%
I also would like a shadow below the
我也想要一个阴影下面的
text
文本
so I duplicate inkscape I click on black
所以我复制了Inkscape我点击了黑色
I set blur to 10 percent
我将模糊设置为10%
I call the path Shadow I press Ctrl and
我将路径命名为阴影，然后按下Ctrl键
drag it down I click on Lower to bottom
将其向下拖动我点击向下
I can also move the Shadow with my arrow
我也可以用我的箭移动阴影
keys to move in smaller increments hold
以较小增量移动的关键点保持不变
the ALT key while pressing the arrow
按住箭头的同时按Alt键
keys finally I will place a shadow below
最后，我将在下面放置一个阴影
the whole text object I duplicate dark
整个文本对象我复制为深色
blue I drag it on the top of the layer I
蓝色我把它拖到我的层的顶部
call the path Shadow below I make it
把下面的小路称为阴影，我做到了
black I set blur to 30. I press Ctrl and
黑色我将模糊设置为30。我按Ctrl键，然后
drag the shadow down I click on Lower to
将阴影向下拖动，然后单击向下
bottom and with my arrow keys I can
底部，用我的箭头键我可以
position The Shadow
定位阴影